# Ezra Piyachanokwong

Software Developer

## Profile

New Graduation who has experience with Customer Service 1 years, Currently Studying in Junior software developer. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, and collaborate in a team setting.

## Employment History

Customer Services Officer at Ngern Tid Lor Pub Co., Ltd, Bangkok December 2020 — February 2021

- Worked to achieve high customer satisfaction rates by providing optimal customer service.
- Achieved and consistently exceeded revenue quota through product and service promotion during routine calls.
- Responded to customer requests for products, services and company information.

## Sales Executive at Siam Nissan BKK Co.,Ltd., Samut Prakan

July 2020 — October 2020

- Reviewing sales performance
- Negotiating contracts and packages
- · Working towards monthly or annual targets.

### Education

## Junior Software Developer, Generation Thailand, Bangkok

January 2022 — April 2022

- · Soft Skills
  - Effectively problem solve to identify solutions to resolve project related issues.
  - Effectively communicate and collaborate with coworkers and other stakeholders using a variety of platforms
  - Behavioral Skills Management (Growth Mindset, Persistence, Personal -Responsibility, Teamwork, and ETC.)
- Technical Skills
  - HTML + CSS
  - JavaScript
  - React+ReactDOM

# Bachelor of Science Information Technology for Design, Silpakorn University, Phetchaburi

August 2015 — May 2019

- · Character Design
- 2D & 3D Motion Design
- Interactive Media
- · Coding & Programing

### **Details**

Bangkok Thailand +66 91099427 ezrapiya.th@gmail.com

Date of birth 13/05/1997

Nationality Thai

### Links

https://fb.me/EzraKanoon https://add-spotify-playlist.netlify.app https://ezra31448.github.io

### **Skills**

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

Git

#### **Hobbies**

Swimming, Gymkhana, Travelling

### Languages

Thai

English